Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Yearbooks MC.304
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Collection of Yearbooks
1887-2012
New York University Archives
New York University
MC.304
108 Linear Feet in 891 volumes, 28 record cartons, 9 manuscript boxes, 6 half manuscript boxes, and 2 folders in a shared manuscript box.
This collection contains yearbooks dating from 1887 to 2012 issued by New York University and its component schools. These yearbooks typically document graduating seniors (with portraits), administrators and faculty, clubs and other student organizations, and athletics. The collection also contains registers of incoming freshmen for certain schools. While the collection is extensive, it is not comprehensive, and there may be published yearbooks that are not included in this collection.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; provenance is unknown. Additional items were donated by various individuals between March 2018 and September 2022; the accession numbers associated with these gifts is 2019.078, 2020.004, 2020.020, 2022.036, 2022.080, and 2023.038.
Existence and Location of Copies
Additional duplicate copies of yearbooks are held in the collection of New York University Publications (preservation copies) (RG 1.0).
Arrangement
The collection is organized into series based on the New York University Archives's record group classification system. Titles for the record groups are based on the school or program's current official name (as of 2019). For example, School of Commerce yearbooks are included as part of the Stern School of Business record group.
Yearbooks are arranged chronologically within these record groups.
Historical Note
Although the earliest yearbook in this collection dates to 1887, the University did not start regularly producing yearbooks until the 1890s. The University's various component schools started issuing yearbooks for their own student bodies starting in the early 20th century. Through the 1930s, many of the yearbooks were produced by the Junior class. As of 2019, NYU is no longer producing yearbooks.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains yearbooks dating from 1887 to 2012 issued by New York University and its component schools. These yearbooks typically document graduating seniors (with portraits), administrators and faculty, clubs and other student organizations, and athletics. The collection also contains registers of incoming freshmen for certain schools. While the collection is extensive, it is not comprehensive, and there may be published yearbooks that are not included in this collection.
Student activities.; Yearbooks; College sports.
- All-University (RG 1)
  - The Lyre, 1887 (Volume The Lyre 1887)
- University College of Arts and Science and the College of Engineering (University Heights) (RG 18 and RG 24)
  - The Violet, 1890 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - The Violet, 1891 (Volume The Violet 1891)
  - The Violet, 1892 (Volume The Violet 1892)
  - The Violet, 1893 (Volume The Violet 1893)
  - The Violet, 1894 (Volume The Violet 1894)
  - The Violet, 1895 (Volume The Violet 1895)
  - The Violet, 1896 (Volume The Violet 1896, Box 41, Folder 1)
  - The Violet, 1897 (Volume The Violet 1897, Box 41, Folder 2)
  - The Violet, 1898 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - The Violet, 1899 (Volume The Violet 1899)
  - The Violet, 1900 (Volume The Violet 1900)
  - The Violet, 1901 (Volume The Violet 1901, Box 36)
  - The Violet, 1902 (Volume The Violet 1902)
  - The Violet, 1903 (Volume The Violet 1903)
  - The Violet, 1904 (Volume The Violet 1904)
  - The Violet, 1905 (Volume The Violet 1905)
  - The Violet, 1906 (Volume The Violet 1906)
  - The Violet, 1907 (Volume The Violet 1907)
  - The Violet, 1908 (Volume The Violet 1908)
  - The Violet, 1909 (Volume The Violet 1909)
  - The Violet, 1910 (Volume The Violet 1910)
  - The Violet, 1911 (Volume The Violet 1911, Box 36)
  - The Violet, 1912 (Volume The Violet 1912)
  - The Violet, 1913 (Volume The Violet 1913)
  - The Violet, 1914 (Volume The Violet 1914)
  - The Violet, 1915 (Volume The Violet 1915)
  - The Violet, 1916 (Volume The Violet 1916)
  - The Violet, 1917 (Volume The Violet 1917)
  - The Violet, 1918 (Volume The Violet 1918)
  - The Violet, 1919 (Volume The Violet 1919)
  - The Violet, 1920 (Volume The Violet 1920)
  - The Violet, 1921 (Volume The Violet 1921)
  - The Violet, 1922 (Volume The Violet 1922)
  - The Violet, 1923 (Volume The Violet 1923)
  - The Violet, 1924 (Volume The Violet 1924)
  - The Violet, 1925 (Volume The Violet 1925)
  - The Violet, 1926 (Volume The Violet 1926, Box 41, Folder 3)
  - The Violet, 1927 (Volume The Violet 1927)
  - The Violet, 1928 (Volume The Violet 1928)
  - The Violet, 1929 (Volume The Violet 1929)
  - The Violet, 1930 (Volume The Violet 1930)
  - The Violet, 1931 (Volume The Violet 1931)
  - The Violet, 1932 (Volume The Violet 1932)
  - The Violet, 1933 (Volume The Violet 1933)
  - The Violet, 1934 (Volume The Violet 1934)
  - The Violet, 1935 (Volume The Violet 1935)
  - The Violet, 1936 (Volume The Violet 1936)
  - The Violet, 1937 (Volume The Violet 1937)
  - The Violet, 1938 (Volume The Violet 1938)
  - The Violet, 1939 (Volume The Violet 1939)
  - The Violet, 1940 (Volume The Violet 1940)
  - The Violet, 1941 (Volume The Violet 1941)
  - The Violet, 1942 (Volume The Violet 1942)
  - The Violet, 1943 (Volume The Violet 1943)
  - The Violet, 1944 (Volume The Violet 1944)
  - The Violet, 1945 (Volume The Violet 1945)
  - The Violet, 1946 (Volume The Violet 1946, Box 42)
  - The Violet, 1947 (Volume The Violet 1947)
  - The Violet, 1948 (Volume The Violet 1948)
  - The Violet, 1949 (Volume The Violet 1949)
  - The Violet, 1950 (Volume The Violet 1950, Box 37)
  - The Violet, 1951 (Volume The Violet 1951)
  - The Violet, 1952 (Volume The Violet 1952)
  - The Violet, 1953 (Volume The Violet 1953)
  - The Violet, 1954 (Volume The Violet 1954)
  - The Violet, 1955 (Volume The Violet 1955)
  - The Violet, 1956 (Volume The Violet 1956)
  - The Violet, 1957 (Volume The Violet 1957)
  - The Violet, 1958 (Volume The Violet 1958)
  - The Violet, 1959 (Volume The Violet 1959)
  - The Violet, 1960 (Volume The Violet 1960)
  - The Violet, 1961 (Volume The Violet 1961)
  - The Violet, 1962 (Volume The Violet 1962)
  - The Violet, 1963 (Volume The Violet 1963)
  - The Violet, 1964 (Volume The Violet 1964)
  - The Violet, 1965 (Volume The Violet 1965)
  - The Violet, 1966 (Volume The Violet 1966, Box 35)
  - The Violet, 1967 (Volume The Violet 1967)
  - The Violet, 1968 (Volume The Violet 1968)
  - The Violet, 1969 (Volume The Violet 1969)
  - The Violet, 1970 (Volume The Violet 1970)
  - The Violet, 1971 (Volume The Violet 1971)
  - The Violet, 1972 (Volume The Violet 1972)
  - The Violet, 1973 (Volume The Violet 1973)
  - The Senior Violet, 1932 (Box 42)
- College of Arts and Sciences (Washington Square) (RG 19)
  - The Album, 1922 (Volume The Album 1922)
  - The Album, 1924 (Box 42)
  - The Album, 1925 (Volume The Album 1925)
  - The Album, 1926 (Volume The Album 1926)
  - The Album, 1927 (Volume The Album 1927)
  - The Senior Album, 1927 (Box 43)
  - The Album, 1928 (Volume The Album 1928)
  - The Album, 1929 (Volume The Album 1929)
  - The Album, 1930 (Volume The Album 1930, Box 35)
  - The Album, 1931 (Volume The Album 1931)
  - The Album, 1932 (Volume The Album 1932)
  - The Album, 1933 (Volume The Album 1933)
  - The Album, 1934 (Volume The Album 1934)
  - The Album, 1935 (Volume The Album 1935)
  - The Album, 1936 (Volume The Album 1936)
  - The Album, 1937 (Volume The Album 1937)
  - The Violet News, 1937 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    The file contains a publication about the 1937 edition of The Violet, the yearbook for the College of Arts and Science.
  - The Album, 1938 (Volume The Album 1937, Box 42)
  - The Album, 1939 (Volume The Album 1939)
  - The Album, 1940 (Volume The Album 1940)
  - The Album, 1941 (Volume The Album 1941)
  - The Album, 1942 (Volume The Album 1942)
  - The Album, 1943 (Volume The Album 1943)
  - The Album, 1944 (Volume The Album 1944)
  - The Album, 1945 (Volume The Album 1945)
  - The Album, 1946 (Volume The Album 1946)
  - The Album, 1947 (Volume The Album 1947)
  - The Album, 1948 (Volume The Album 1948)
  - The Album, 1949 (Volume The Album 1949)
  - The Album, 1950 (Volume The Album 1950)
  - The Album, 1951 (Volume The Album 1951)
  - The Album, 1952 (Volume The Album 1952)
  - The Album, 1953 (Volume The Album 1953)
  - The Album, 1954 (Volume The Album 1954)
  - The Album, 1955 (Volume The Album 1955)
  - The Album, 1956 (Volume The Album 1956)
  - The Album, 1957 (Volume The Album 1957)
  - The Album, 1958 (Volume The Album 1958)
  - The Album, 1959 (Volume The Album 1959)
  - The Album, 1960 (Volume The Album 1960)
  - The Album, 1961 (Volume The Album 1961)
  - The Album, 1962 (Volume The Album 1962)
  - The Album, 1963 (Volume The Album 1963)
  - The Album, 1964 (Volume The Album 1964)
  - The Album, 1964 (Volume The Album 1964)
  - The Album, 1965 (Volume The Album 1965)
  - The Album, 1966 (Volume The Album 1966)
  - The Album, 1967 (Volume The Album 1967)
  - The Album, 1968 (Volume The Album 1968)
  - The Album, 1969 (Volume The Album 1969)
  - The Album, 1973 (Volume The Album 1973)
  - The Album, 1974 (Volume The Album 1974)
  - The Album, 1975 (Volume The Album 1975)
  - The Album, 1976 (Volume The Album 1976)
  - The Torch, 1977 (Volume The Torch 1977)
  - The Torch, 1978 (Volume The Torch 1978)
  - The Torch, 1979 (Box 1)
  - The Torch, 1980 (Volume The Torch 1980)
  - The Torch, 1981 (Volume The Torch 1981)
  - The Torch, 1982 (Volume The Torch 1982)
  - The Torch, 1983 (Volume The Torch 1983)
  - The Torch, 1984 (Volume The Torch 1984)
  - The Torch, 1985 (Volume The Torch 1985)
  - The Torch, 1986 (Volume The Torch 1986)
  - The Torch, 1987 (Volume The Torch 1987)
  - The Freshman Register, 1987 (Volume The CAS Freshman Register 1987)
  - The Torch, 1988 (Volume The Torch 1988)
  - The Freshman Register, 1988 (Volume The CAS Freshman Register 1988)
  - The Torch, 1989 (Volume The Torch 1989)
  - The Freshman Register, 1989 (Volume The CAS Freshman Register 1989)
  - The Torch, 1990 (Volume The Torch 1990)
  - The Freshman Register, 1990 (Volume The CAS Freshman Register 1990)
  - The Torch, 1991 (Volume The Torch 1991)
  - The Freshman Register, 1991 (Volume The CAS Freshman Register 1991)
  - The Torch, 1992 (Volume The Torch 1992)
  - The Torch, 1993 (Volume The Torch 1993)
  - The Freshman Register, 1993 (Volume The CAS Freshman Register 1993)
  - The Torch, 1994 (Volume The Torch 1994)
  - The Freshman Register, 1994 (Volume The CAS Freshman Register 1994)
  - The Torch, 1995 (Volume The Torch 1995)
  - The Freshman Register, 1996 (Volume The CAS Freshman Register 1996)
  - The Torch, 1998 (Volume The Torch 1998)
  - The Torch, 1999 (Volume The Torch 1999)
  - The Torch, 2000 (Volume The Torch 2000)
  - The Torch, 2001 (Volume The Torch 2001)
  - The Torch, 2002 (Volume The Torch 2002)
  - CAS Yearbook Spring supplement, 2002 (Box 1)
  - The Torch, 2003 (Volume The Torch 2003)
  - CAS Yearbook Spring supplement, 2003 (Box 1, Box 43)
  - The Torch, 2004 (Volume The Torch 2004)
  - The Torch, 2005 (Volume The Torch 2005)
- The Evening Division of Washington Square College (RG 19.13)
  - The Owl, 1930 (Volume The Owl 1930)
  - The Owl, 1931 (Volume The Owl 1931)
  - The Owl, 1932 (Volume The Owl 1932)
- School of Law (RG 22)
  - Certiorari writ, 1953 (Volume Centiorari writ 1953)
  - Certiorari writ, 1954 (Volume Centiorari writ 1954)
  - Certiorari writ, 1955 (Volume Centiorari writ 1955)
  - Certiorari writ, 1956 (Volume Centiorari writ 1956)
  - Certiorari writ, 1957 (Volume Centiorari writ 1957)
  - Certiorari writ, 1958 (Volume Centiorari writ 1958)
  - The Class Book, 1959 (Volume The Class Book 1959)
  - The Class Book, 1960 (Volume The Class Book 1960)
  - The Yearbook, 1960 (Volume The Yearbook 1960)
  - School of Law First-Year Student Portrait Booklets, 1972-1973, 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - School of Law Graduate Division Portrait Booklets, 1975-1976, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- School of Medicine (RG 23)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1922 (Volume The Bellevue Violet 1922)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1925 (Volume The Bellevue Violet 1925)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1926 (Volume The Bellevue Violet 1926)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1927 (Volume The Bellevue Violet 1927)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1928 (Volume The Bellevue Violet 1928)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1929 (Volume The Bellevue Violet 1929)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1930 (Volume The Bellevue Violet 1930)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1931 (Volume The Bellevue Violet 1931)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1932 (Volume The Bellevue Violet 1932)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1933 (Volume The Bellevue Violet 1933)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1934 (Volume The Bellevue Violet 1934)
  - The Medical Violet, 1935 (Volume The Medical Violet 1935)
  - The Medical Violet, 1936 (Volume The Medical Violet 1936)
  - The Medical Violet, 1937 (Volume The Medical Violet 1937)
  - The Medical Violet, 1938 (Volume The Medical Violet 1938)
  - The Medical Violet, 1939 (Volume The Medical Violet 1939)
  - The Medical Violet, 1940 (Volume The Medical Violet 1940)
  - The Medical Violet, 1941 (Volume The Medical Violet 1941)
  - The Medical Violet, 1942 (Volume The Medical Violet 1942)
  - The Medical Violet, 1943 (Volume The Medical Violet 1943)
  - The Medical Violet, 1944 (Volume The Medical Violet 1944)
  - The Medical Violet, 1945 (Volume The Medical Violet 1945)
  - The Medical Violet, 1946 (Volume The Medical Violet 1946)
  - The Medical Violet, 1947 (Volume The Medical Violet 1947)
  - The Medical Violet, 1948 (Volume The Medical Violet 1948)
  - The Medical Violet, 1949 (Volume The Medical Violet 1949)
  - The Medical Violet, 1950 (Volume The Medical Violet 1950)
  - The Medical Violet, 1951 (Volume The Medical Violet 1951)
  - The Medical Violet, 1952 (Volume The Medical Violet 1952)
  - The Medical Violet, 1953 (Volume The Medical Violet 1953)
  - The Medical Violet, 1954 (Volume The Medical Violet 1954)
  - The Medical Violet, 1955 (Volume The Medical Violet 1955)
  - The Medical Violet, 1956 (Volume The Medical Violet 1956)
  - The Medical Violet, 1957 (Volume The Medical Violet 1957)
  - The Medical Violet, 1958 (Volume The Medical Violet 1958)
  - The Medical Violet, 1959 (Volume The Medical Violet 1959)
  - The Medical Violet, 1960 (Volume The Medical Violet 1960)
  - The Medical Violet, 1961 (Volume The Medical Violet 1961)
  - The Medical Violet, 1962 (Volume The Medical Violet 1962)
  - The Medical Violet, 1963 (Volume The Medical Violet 1963)
  - The Medical Violet, 1964 (Volume The Medical Violet 1964)
  - The Medical Violet, 1965 (Volume The Medical Violet 1965)
  - The Medical Violet, 1966 (Volume The Medical Violet 1966)
  - The Medical Violet, 1967 (Volume The Medical Violet 1967)
  - The Medical Violet, 1968 (Volume The Medical Violet 1968)
  - The Medical Violet, 1969 (Volume The Medical Violet 1969)
  - The Medical Violet, 1970 (Volume The Medical Violet 1970)
  - The Medical Violet, 1971 (Volume The Medical Violet 1971)
  - The Medical Violet, 1972 (Volume The Medical Violet 1972)
  - The Medical Violet, 1973 (Volume The Medical Violet 1973)
  - The Medical Violet, 1974 (Volume The Medical Violet 1974)
  - The Medical Violet, 1975 (Volume The Medical Violet 1975)
  - The Medical Violet, 1976 (Volume The Medical Violet 1976)
  - The Medical Violet, 1977 (Volume The Medical Violet 1977)
  - The Medical Violet, 1978 (Volume The Medical Violet 1978)
  - The Medical Violet, 1979 (Volume The Medical Violet 1979)
  - The Medical Violet, 1980 (Volume The Medical Violet 1980)
  - The Medical Violet, 1981 (Volume The Medical Violet 1981)
  - The Medical Violet, 1982 (Volume The Medical Violet 1982)
  - The Medical Violet, 1983 (Volume The Medical Violet 1983)
  - The Medical Violet, 1984 (Volume The Medical Violet 1984)
  - The Medical Violet, 1985 (Volume The Medical Violet 1985)
  - The Medical Violet, 1986 (Volume The Medical Violet 1986)
  - The Medical Violet, 1987 (Volume The Medical Violet 1987)
  - The Medical Violet, 1988 (Volume The Medical Violet 1988)
  - The Medical Violet, 1989 (Volume The Medical Violet 1989)
  - The Medical Violet, 1990 (Volume The Medical Violet 1990)
  - The Medical Violet, 1991 (Volume The Medical Violet 1991)
  - The Medical Violet, 1992 (Volume The Medical Violet 1992)
  - The Medical Violet, 1993 (Volume The Medical Violet 1993)
  - The Medical Violet, 1994 (Volume The Medical Violet 1994)
  - The Medical Violet, 1995 (Volume The Medical Violet 1995)
  - The Medical Violet, 1996 (Volume The Medical Violet 1996)
  - The Medical Violet, 1997 (Volume The Medical Violet 1997)
  - The Medical Violet, 1998 (Volume The Medical Violet 1998)
  - The Medical Violet, 1999 (Volume The Medical Violet 1999)
  - The Medical Violet, 2000 (Volume The Medical Violet 2000)
  - The Medical Violet, 2001 (Volume The Medical Violet 2001)
  - The Medical Violet, 2003 (Volume The Medical Violet 2003)
  - The Medical Violet, 2004 (Volume The Medical Violet 2004)
  - The Medical Violet, 2005 (Volume The Medical Violet 2005)
  - The Medical Violet, 2006 (Volume The Medical Violet 2006)
  - The Medical Violet, 2007 (Volume The Medical Violet 2007)
  - The Medical Violet, 2008 (Volume The Medical Violet 2008)
  - The Medical Violet, 2012 (Volume The Medical Violet 2012)
- The School of Engineering Evening Division (RG 24)
  - The Mast, 1939 (Volume The Mast 1939)
  - The Mast, 1941 (Volume The Mast 1941)
  - The Mast, 1942 (Volume The Mast 1942)
  - The Mast, 1943 (Volume The Mast 1943)
- The School of Engineering Department of Meteorology (RG 24)
  - The Synopsis, 1943 (Volume The Synopsis 1943)
  - The Synopsis (1-A), 1944 (Volume The Synopsis (1-A) 1944)
  - The Synopsis (2-A), 1944 (Volume The Synopsis (2-A) 1944)
- College of Dentistry (RG 25)
  - The Dental Violet, 1924 (Volume The Dental Violet 1924)
  - The Dental Violet, 1926 (Volume The Dental Violet 1926)
  - The Dental Violet, 1927 (Volume The Dental Violet 1927)
  - The Dental Violet, 1928 (Volume The Dental Violet 1928)
  - The Dental Violet, 1929 (Volume The Dental Violet 1929)
  - The Dental Violet, 1930 (Volume The Dental Violet 1930)
  - The Dental Violet, 1931 (Volume The Dental Violet 1931)
  - The Dental Violet, 1932 (Volume The Dental Violet 1932)
  - The Dental Violet, 1933 (Volume The Dental Violet 1933)
  - The Dental Violet, 1934 (Volume The Dental Violet 1934)
  - The Dental Violet, 1935 (Volume The Dental Violet 1935)
  - The Dental Violet, 1936 (Volume The Dental Violet 1936)
  - The Dental Violet, 1937 (Volume The Dental Violet 1937)
  - The Dental Violet, 1938 (Volume The Dental Violet 1938)
  - The Dental Violet, 1939 (Volume The Dental Violet 1939)
  - The Dental Violet, 1940 (Volume The Dental Violet 1940)
  - The Dental Violet, 1941 (Volume The Dental Violet 1941)
  - The Dental Violet, 1942 (Volume The Dental Violet 1942)
  - The Dental Violet, 1943 (Volume The Dental Violet 1943)
  - The Dental Violet (December), 1943 (Volume The Dental Violet December 1943)
  - The Dental Violet, 1944 (Volume The Dental Violet 1944)
  - The Dental Violet (September), 1944 (Volume The Dental Violet September 1944)
  - The Dental Violet, 1945 (Volume The Dental Violet 1945)
  - The Dental Violet, 1946 (Volume The Dental Violet 1946)
  - The Dental Violet, 1947 (Volume The Dental Violet 1947)
  - The Dental Violet, 1948 (Volume The Dental Violet 1948)
  - The Dental Violet, 1949 (Volume The Dental Violet 1949)
  - The Dental Violet, 1950 (Volume The Dental Violet 1950)
  - The Dental Violet, 1951 (Volume The Dental Violet 1951)
  - The Dental Violet, 1952 (Volume The Dental Violet 1952)
  - The Dental Violet, 1953 (Volume The Dental Violet 1953)
  - The Dental Violet, 1954 (Volume The Dental Violet 1954)
  - The Dental Violet, 1955 (Volume The Dental Violet 1955)
  - The Dental Violet, 1956 (Volume The Dental Violet 1956)
  - The Dental Violet, 1957 (Volume The Dental Violet 1957)
  - The Dental Violet, 1958 (Volume The Dental Violet 1958)
  - The Dental Violet, 1959 (Volume The Dental Violet 1959)
  - The Dental Violet, 1960 (Volume The Dental Violet 1960)
  - The Dental Violet, 1961 (Volume The Dental Violet 1961)
  - The Dental Violet, 1962 (Volume The Dental Violet 1962)
  - The Dental Violet, 1963 (Volume The Dental Violet 1963)
  - The Dental Violet, 1964 (Volume The Dental Violet 1964)
  - The Dental Violet, 1965 (Volume The Dental Violet 1965)
  - The Dental Violet, 1966 (Volume The Dental Violet 1966)
  - The Dental Violet, 1967 (Volume The Dental Violet 1967)
  - The Dental Violet, 1968 (Volume The Dental Violet 1968)
  - The Dental Violet, 1969 (Volume The Dental Violet 1969)
  - The Dental Violet, 1970 (Volume The Dental Violet 1970)
  - The Dental Violet, 1971 (Volume The Dental Violet 1971)
  - The Dental Violet, 1972 (Volume The Dental Violet 1972)
  - The Dental Violet, 1973 (Volume The Dental Violet 1973)
  - The Dental Violet, 1974 (Volume The Dental Violet 1974)
  - The Dental Violet, 1974-1975 (Volume The Dental Violet 1974-1975)
  - The Dental Violet, 1975 (Volume The Dental Violet 1975)
  - The Dental Violet, 1976 (Volume The Dental Violet 1976)
  - The Dental Violet, 1977 (Volume The Dental Violet 1977)
  - The Dental Violet, 1978 (Volume The Dental Violet 1978)
  - The Dental Violet, 1980 (Volume The Dental Violet 1980)
  - The Dental Violet, 1981 (Volume The Dental Violet 1981)
  - The Dental Violet, 1982 (Volume The Dental Violet 1982)
  - The Dental Violet, 1983 (Volume The Dental Violet 1983)
  - The Dental Violet, 1984 (Volume The Dental Violet 1984, Box 37)
  - The Dental Violet, 1985 (Volume The Dental Violet 1985)
  - The Dental Violet, 1986 (Volume The Dental Violet 1986)
  - The Dental Violet, 1987 (Volume The Dental Violet 1987)
  - The Dental Violet, 1988 (Volume The Dental Violet 1988)
  - The Dental Violet, 1990 (Volume The Dental Violet 1990)
  - The Death Violet, 1992 (Volume The Dental Violet 1992)
  - The Dental Violet, 1994 (Volume The Dental Violet 1994)
  - The Dental Violet, 1995 (Volume The Dental Violet 1995)
  - The Dental Violet, 1996 (Volume The Dental Violet 1996)
  - The Dental Violet, 1997 (Volume The Dental Violet 1997)
  - The Dental Violet, 1998 (Volume The Dental Violet 1998)
  - The Dental Violet, 1999 (Volume The Dental Violet 1999)
  - The Dental Violet, 2000 (Volume The Dental Violet 2000)
  - The Dental Violet, 2001 (Volume The Dental Violet 2001)
  - The Dental Violet, 2002 (Volume The Dental Violet 2002)
  - The Dental Violet, 2003 (Volume The Dental Violet 2003)
  - The Dental Violet, 2004 (Volume The Dental Violet 2004)
  - The Dental Violet, 2005 (Volume The Dental Violet 2005)
  - The Dental Violet, 2006 (Volume The Dental Violet 2006)
  - The Dental Violet, 2007 (Volume The Dental Violet 2007)
  - The Dental Violet, 2008 (Volume The Dental Violet 2008)
  - The Dental Violet, 2009 (Volume The Dental Violet 2009)
  - The Dental Violet, 2010 (Volume The Dental Violet 2010)
- Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development (RG 26)
  - The Prometheus, 1929 (Volume The Prometheus 1929)
  - The Education Violet, 1931 (Volume The Education Violet 1931, Box 35)
  - The Education Violet, 1932 (Volume The Education Violet 1932)
  - The Education Violet, 1933 (Volume The Education Violet 1933)
  - The Education Violet, 1934 (Volume The Education Violet 1934)
  - The Education Violet, 1934 (Volume The Education Violet 1934)
  - The Education Violet, 1935 (Volume The Education Violet 1935)
  - The Education Violet (The Seniorama), 1936 (Box 2)
  - The Education Violet, 1937 (Volume The Education Violet 1937)
  - The Education Violet (Summer), 1937 (Box 2)
  - The Education Violet, 1938 (Volume The Education Violet 1938)